Hey friends, just wanted to give you a heads up that I am once again taking...
Hey, what the heck?
Surely you jest.
I thought you said you'd take a rest.
No, that starts tomorrow.
She's just telling them about how she doesn't post YouTube videos in January.
Also, why do you carry around a harp if you're just gonna do poetry?
Shouldn't you sing or something?
Oh, you don't want to hear her sing, trust me.
Did you just come out of the closet?
Right, you know.
You really should rest.
You look tired.
Wow, rude.
And it's not really a rest, unfortunately.
I used January to do all my business planning for the year.
And I still post on social media, so it's not like I'm gone gone.
Should they follow you on Instagram?
TikTok, Facebook, Blue Sky?
Patreon?
It's Patreon.
You're not very good at poetry either, are you?
Yeah, I'll be posting in all those places.
But regardless, I'll be back here in February with more videos.
It's just a few weeks.
It'll fly by.
And I can carry quite a tune.
Unlike your magic, you buffoon.
Hey, how dare you?
You guys are giving me a headache.
You probably have an evil spirit trapped in your head.
Want me to cut it out of your skull?
You know what?
On second thought, I will start my break now.
Everybody out.